number 25 okay meditation 25 page 11
now the tenth message Cal is that you're
supposed to take refuge three times
every day and three times every night
that's 1/10 recive Val we'll talk about
it later but the good news is if you
understand what taking refuge is
especially if you understand that taking
refuge is deciding and not to tell your
husband how stupid he is it's in you to
do it six times a day okay
someone will irritate you six times a
day that's why we get married it's
automatic in your own house you don't
have to go anywhere okay six times a day
your partner will expect a big upset or
a little upset I mean Michael Dunn never
does I know but we can borrow somebody I
know
anyway if you understand what refuge
really means this meditation can I
remember the pen six times a day yes
okay no problem okay otherwise if refuge
means I have to go to the temple and
burn incense then six times a day is a
problem I won't have time to do anything
else
okay it doesn't mean that it means
understanding emptiness six times a day
okay and and I don't know if I Drive
from my house to village of Oak Creek
six people will irritate me in traffic
then I'm like thank you now I'm done for
the day
you know kingmakers driving me home
okay I can cover it in just about 25
minutes Jack I can do my six times
refuse seriously sometimes I forget I
just get pissed off if you just remember
all that's coming from me why do I have
to see people breaking the rules so
awesome there's a joke in then BCI
what's the joke I don't know why I have
to see somebody talking too much name
what is that makes like okay there's a
BCI junkie I don't know why I have to
see people eating sweets all day okay
so 25 is just you know you will get
sunburned or some bug will get into your
den and keep you up for two hours and
you know something will happen during
between don't worry demons don't like
people doing retreats they will come the
minute you put up your what's the marker
it's an advertisement for demons come to
this house someone's trying to
meditating that's the real meaning of
this Omaha
okay come bother me you know something
will happen last time what happened I
remember the handle came off of
somebody's bath tub and all the water
for every house is pushing out of them
one bathroom you know
me and Tim Ellen was it you and me we
had a good time that night gal say with
the hero him and me were walking we're
like oh my god nobody will have any
water in about half an hour and okay the
minute you start during retreat
something will happen and because they
want you to spend the rest of your life
looking at cat videos on YouTube okay
they don't want you during retreat okay
they don't want you to be retrieved the
demons don't like it when people do
retreat and and very very serious things
will happen to people in retreat okay
and we proved it here and it happens
okay so when stuff happens you should
feel proud you know you know penny did
you get any obstacles no guess not
everything went smooth
I got obstacles demons thought I was
going to do something cool so they came
to my cabin and they left you alone you
know i attracted demons i must have been
doing some good practice you didn't have
any demons don't worry next time if you
work hard you can get some chemo okay
okay so that's demons are good because
it gives you a chance to take refuge
okay then you can keep your refuge Val
if the demons come six times a day you
should be happy yes madam yeah number
one demons don't like it it's called
goal number in Tibetan as a special word
if you stick your head up out of the
poopoo I'd like to get out
they are looking to see if anyone is not
looking at cat videos all day you know
they're like I don't want to look at
Cavaliers go back to the cat video you
know there when you stick your head up
its called blowing them up they won't
take you back down okay why they don't
like it is bad deed number nine because
of our human tendency to be unhappy when
other people succeed
we are so happy when a movie star
Oh Brad Pitt divorced Angela and Angela
Julie who really tell me he threw
something at her oh really
now you can hear it like for two hours
on the lawyers are you know talking
about what he threw at her and people
why it is it on the radio why they put
it on the internet because we like it oh
really
tell me more getting here or just mister
you know and okay and that causes demons
yeah the demons are coming from us
because we're so interested about movie
stars troubles okay all right and and I
am too I mean it's almost unconscious
it's it's part of us you know what was
that recently anyway we loved oh those
two guys got fired in the government
yeah one guy oh did you hear he was
talking to the restaurants but he said
he wasn't talking to the restaurant and
so they fired him oh really tell me
Mariana and the other guy was just mean
all the time anyway Oh tell me more
which one What did he say who fired her
you know like that okay